THE WEB CONTENT ACCESSIBILITY GUIDELINES ALSO CALLED WCAG
THE CRITERION THAT WE ARE GOING TO SPEAK TODAY IS WHAT I HAVE CHOSEN
SUCCESS CRITERION 2.4.6 TALKING ABOUT HEADERS AND LABELS
WE HAVE A VERY SIMPLE LINK THAT TAKES US TO THE OFFICIAL PAGE
BUT WE START THE HEADERS RIGHT AWAY
H1 H2 H3 HEADERS TO H6
THEIR GREATEST DIFFERENCE IS THE SIZE OF THE WORD
WHICH IS INSIDE THESE HEADERS IN FACT
WE CAN SEE IN THE PHOTO BELOW THE TEXT
THE INSCRIPTION IN THE HEADER
H1 WILL BE MUCH BIGGER
COMPARED TO THE H6
WHEREAS H3,H4,H5 ARE QUANTITIES
WHICH ARE IN THE MIDDLE H1 AND H6
WHICH ARE USED FOR THE TEXT
WHILE H1 IS USUALLY USED
FOR A TITLE IT IS A PART WHICH MUST BE VERY VISIBLE
TO THE USER VISITING THE SITE
H STANDS FOR HEADING I MEAN THE HEAD
THERE ARE DIFFERENT TYPES OF HEADERS
IN FACT, THERE ARE PARAGRAPHS HEADERS
WHICH ARE CALLED P WHICH IN FACT P STANDS FOR PARAGRAPH
THAT LATER WE WILL SEE WHAT CHANGES FROM H1 H2 AND P
PARAGRAPH IS THE BASIC UNIT WHICH SUBDIVIDES A TEXT
ALSO CALLED TAG
WHAT DOES THE PARAGRAPH DO?
LEAVE AN EMPTY LINE BEFORE OPENING
AND AFTER ITS CLOSURE
THEN TITLES ARE VERY IMPORTANT
IN FACT, PEOPLE WITH DISABLES OR SHORT MEMORY
IT IS VERY IMPORTANT TO HAVE CLEAR TITLES
TO GET YOU BACK TO THE POINT
INITIAL OR WHERE THEY WERE LOST
OR A KEYWORD I MEAN
A WORD THAT REMINDS ME OF WHAT THEY WERE DOING
TITLES HAVE MORE THAN THIS PURPOSE
BUT THEY ARE ALSO INTENDED FOR READING
OR MAKE PEOPLE SURF THE SITE MUCH MORE SMOOTHLY
BECAUSE HAVING VERY CLEAR AND DEFINED TITLES
WE ALSO HAVE A VERY CLEAR AND CLEAN SITE
LET’S GO AND SEE THE HEADERS RIGHT AWAY
WE BEGIN TO OPEN A REAL WEBSITE
YOU NEED THE HEAD INSIDE
WE FIND THE TITLE, THE TITLE TAG
THE TITLE AS MENTIONED ABOVE IS VERY IMPORTANT
BUT THIS IS THE TITLE OF THE PAGE WE PUT IN THIS CASE
WCAG... BELOW WE MUST OPEN
LIKE EVERY SITE THE BODY
THE BODY OF THE WEBSITE WE ARE GOING TO CREATE
NOW LET’S TRY THE HEADERS NOW... THE MAIN ONES
IN FACT IF WE GO TO WRITE IN A HEADER
H1 LET’S CALL IT "TEST TEXT"
AND LET’S GO GET AN H6 HEADER
AND WE WRITE THE USUAL TEXT WE CAN GO AND SEE
THAT H1 AS WE SAID IS MUCH BIGGER
COMPARED TO H6
H1 MAY BE USED AS A HEADLINE WHILE H6
A TITLE WITH THESE MAGNITUDES IS NOT VERY GOOD